[PANTING]
(Penny:)Having a little trouble
catching your breath, there?
(Leonard:)No, I'm good. If my P.E. teachers had
told me this is what I was training for...
(Leonard:)...I would have tried a lot harder.
[LAUGHS]
(Penny:)Do or do not, there is no try.
Heh. Did you just quote Star Wars?
(Penny:)I believe I quoted Empire Strikes Back.
Ha, ha. Oh, my God.
I am lying in bed with a beautiful woman
who can quote Yoda.
[PENNY LAUGHS]
[CHUCKLES]
(Leonard:)I love you, Penny.
Uh.... Heh.
(Penny:)Thank you.
(Leonard:)You're welcome.
(Leonard:)-I just wanted to put that out there.
-Oh, yeah. No, I--
(Penny:)-I'm glad.
-Yeah-- Oh, good.
(Leonard:)-Good. Glad is good.
-Yeah.
Ha. Ahem.
(Penny:)No-- Um....
So, heh....
(Penny:)It's getting pretty late.
We should, tsk, go to sleep.
(Penny:)-Yeah.
-Okay.
(Leonard:)Yeah, probably.
(Penny:)-Okay. Good night, sweetie.
-Good night.